<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Intro to Social Data Science</title>
    <link>https://abjer.github.io/isds2020/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Intro to Social Data Science</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>abn@sodas.ku.dk (Andreas Bjerre-Nielsen)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>abn@sodas.ku.dk (Andreas Bjerre-Nielsen)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://abjer.github.io/isds2020/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Course readings</title>
      <link>https://abjer.github.io/isds2020/page/readings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>abn@sodas.ku.dk (Andreas Bjerre-Nielsen)</author>
      <guid>https://abjer.github.io/isds2020/page/readings/</guid>
      <description>Textbook for general introduction to social data science:
 Big by Bit - Social research in the digital age by Matthew J. Salganik [BBB], free online version here.  Textbooks for data science in Python
 Python for Data Analysis, 2nd ed. (2017) by Wes McKinney [PDA] Python Machine Learning, 2nd ed. (2017) by Sebastian Raschka &amp;amp; Vahid Mirjalili [PML]  Preparation and Assignment 0 The course begin with your preparation for the teaching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timeplan</title>
      <link>https://abjer.github.io/isds2020/page/timeplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>abn@sodas.ku.dk (Andreas Bjerre-Nielsen)</author>
      <guid>https://abjer.github.io/isds2020/page/timeplan/</guid>
      <description>This page contains a schedule of the teaching sessions. In general most of the teaching will take place August 10-19, 2020. Each day will contain one-two teaching sessions. Most sessions will follow the daily schedule below:
 Morning session (9-12):  9-11 exercises, 11-12 live lecture (via Zoom - links here)  Lunch break (12-14):  12-13 office hours, optional (via Zoom, booking system will come)  Afternoon session (14-17):  14-16 exercise 16-17 live lecture (via Zoom - links here)   The complete schedule of sessions is listed below with title, lecturer and links to material.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical info</title>
      <link>https://abjer.github.io/isds2020/page/practical/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>abn@sodas.ku.dk (Andreas Bjerre-Nielsen)</author>
      <guid>https://abjer.github.io/isds2020/page/practical/</guid>
      <description>This page contains information about the course groups as well as information on mandatory assignments and exam project.
Place and time The course runs from August 10, 2020 to August 29. See timeplan for teaching schedule.
The teaching format will be a mix of online and teaching on campus.
 All lectures will be online and consist of an on-demand part and live part where questions are answered. Lab/exercise classes will run both online and on-campus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>